A Guide to the John Janney Papers, 1811-1994 (Bulk 1840-1880)
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Books, Periodicals, and Media, 1837-1845, n.d.
  - Periodicals, 1838-1845, n.d.
    - Niles' National Register, 1845. (Box 18)
      April 12, 1845, Fifth Series, No. 6, Vol.XVIII. Vol. LXVIII, Whole No. 1,750
      April 19, 1845, Fifth Series, No. 7, Vol. XVIII. Vol. LXVIII, Whole No. 1,751
      April 26, 1845, Fifth Series, No. 8, Vol. XVIII. Vol. LXVIII, Whole No. 1,752
      May 3, 1845, Fifth Series, No.9, Vol. XVIII. Vol.LXVIII, Whole No. 1,753
      May 10, 1845, Fifth Series, No. 10, Vol. XVII. Vol. LXVIII, Whole No. 1,754
      May 17, 1845, Fifth Series, No. 11, Vol. XVIII. Vol. LXVIII, Whole No. 1,755
      May 24, 1845, Fifth Series, No 12, Vol. XVIII. Vol. LXVIII, Whole No. 1,756
      May 31, 1845, Fifth Series, No. 13, Vol. XVIII. Vol. LXVIII, Whole No. 1,757
      June 14, 1845, Fifth Series, No. 15, Vol. XVIII. Vol.LXVIII, Whole No. 1,759
      June 21, 1845, Fifth Series, No. 16, Vol. XVIII. Vol. LXVIII, Whole No. 1,760
      June 28, 1845, Fifth Series, No. 17, Vol. XVIII. Vol..LXVIII, Whole No. 1,761
      July 5, 1845, Fifth Series, No. 17, Vol. XVIII. Vol. LXVIII, Whole No. 1,762
      July 12, 1845, Fifth Series, No. 19, Vol. XVIII. Vol. LXVIII, Whole No. 1,763
      July 19, 1845, Fifth Series, No. 20, Vol. XVIII. Vol.LXVIII, Whole No. 1,764
      July 26, 1845, Fifth Series, No. 21, Vol. XVIII. Vol. LXVIII, Whole No. 1,765
      August 2, 1842, Fifth Series, No. 22, Vol. XVIII. Vol. LXVIII, Whole NO. 1,766
      August 9, 1845, Fifth Series, No. 23, Vol. XVIII. Vol. LXVII, Whole No. 1,767
      August 16, 1845, Fifth Series, No. 24, Vol. XVIII. Vol. LXVIII, Whole No. 1,768
      August 30, 1845, Fith Series, No. 26, Vol. XVIII. Vol. LXVIII, Whole No. 1,770
  - Other Media
    - Compact disc of Janney images. (Box-folder 19:1)
      Images are also available on Imagebase.
    - Videotape of Janney Collection. (Box-folder 19:2)